[
  {
    "question": "apple",
    "answer": "Pomme"
  },
  {
    "question": "mountain",
    "answer": "Montagne"
  },
  {
    "question": "sea",
    "answer": "Mer"
  },
  {
    "question": "sailboat",
    "answer": "Voilier"
  },
  {
    "question": "piano player",
    "answer": "Pianiste"
  },
  {
    "question": "handcuffs",
    "answer": "Menottes"
  },
  {
    "question": "travel",
    "answer": "Voyage"
  },
  {
    "question": "pistol (gun)",
    "answer": "Pistolet"
  },
  {
    "question": "rocket (space travel)",
    "answer": "Fus√©e"
  },
  {
    "question": "calculator (pocket calculator)",
    "answer": "Calculatrice (de poche)"
  }
]